realgfsexposed.com 2015-03-05

# Porn movies, videos and galleries | DaGFs

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which our company collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the [http://www.dagfs.com](http://www.dagfs.com/) website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by our company.

Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, credit card information. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information, however this may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

How we use collected information

Our Site collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes: 

  * To improve our Site   
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you. 
  * To improve customer service   
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs. 
  * To process transactions   
We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service. 
  * To send periodic emails   
The email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. 

How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

Compliance with children's online privacy protection act

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18.

Changes to this privacy policy

Our Site has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

Disclosures of information

Your name, physical address, phone number and password are considered confidential. However, all information you provide to us may be shared with other third parties as necessary fulfill technical requirement or to comply with applicable law, to cooperate with law enforcement and the court system.

By accepting membership to this site, the subscriber expressly and specifically acknowledges and agrees that it may receive from time to time, email communications from this site or from third?party services. These communications shall be deemed to be opt?in email communications by virtue of the subscriber joining this site. Thru this process, the subscriber’s personal information and data may be disclosed to third?party services

Email opt-in and user communication

The subscriber's e?mail address may be used by the site to communicate special offers and other relevant information such as new services, subscription information, etc. In addition, there may be occasions when a subscriber will be presented with special offers either from the operators of the site or from third?party service, which may include consent to receive e?mail solicitations, communications, newsletters, commercial advertising, or other promotional or special event materials. These communications shall be deemed to be opt?in email communications by virtue of the subscriber joining this site. The subscriber may opt?out of a mailing list by clicking on the removal link located at the bottom of the promotional email or by visiting the site [www.mailgo2.com](http://www.mailgo2.com/)  

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: <http://www.dagfs.com/support>   

This document was last updated on October 22, 2014
